Video

    MLB.TV

    AL East

    AL Central

    AL West

    NL East

    NL Central

    NL West

Log in

MLB Privacy Policy
==================

**The Privacy Policy has been updated as of July 1, 2024. For details on exercising rights under the California Consumer Privacy Act, as amended by the California Privacy Right Act; the Virginia Consumer Data Protection Act; the Colorado Privacy Act; the Connecticut Data Privacy Act; the Utah Consumer Privacy Act; or the Texas Data Privacy and Security Act, [click here](#section-7).**

**PLEASE READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY (THIS “PRIVACY POLICY”) CAREFULLY BEFORE USING THIS WEBSITE, APPLICATION OR ANY OTHER MLB ADVANCED MEDIA, L.P. PRODUCT OR SERVICE.**

MLB Advanced Media, L.P. ("MLB") is the organization that produces and publishes the Official Website of Major League Baseball, which encompasses MLB.com, the Official Websites of the thirty (30) Major League Baseball clubs (collectively "MLB Clubs" and each an "MLB Club"), the Official Website of Minor League Baseball (“MiLB”), which encompasses MiLB.com, the Official Websites of the professional baseball clubs participating in the Professional Development League System pursuant to a Player Development License Agreement (collectively, the MiLB Clubs” and each an “MiLB Club”), and the Official Websites of certain other MLB-related and MiLB-related properties (collectively, this "Website"), downloadable mobile applications (e.g., MLB, Ballpark, MiLB app) available from any other company, entity or person’s (any other company, entity or person referred to in this policy as “Other Company or collectively “Other Companies”) application storefronts ("Application(s)"), mobile games available from Other Companies’ application storefronts (e.g., Beat the Streak, R.B.I. Baseball) ("Mobile Games"), games and other applications available from Other Companies’ social media locations and gaming websites (e.g., MLB Ballpark Empire) ("Social Games" and together with Mobile Games, "Games").

For customers within the European Union and European Economic Area ("EEA"), MLB is the data controller of your personal data, which we also refer to as personal information. To contact us, please see the contact details at the end of this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is applicable to this Website, Applications, Games and all products and services provided and/or distributed (whether via this Website or elsewhere) by MLB which link to this Privacy Policy, all of which will be referred to herein collectively as the "MLB Properties" and individually as an "MLB Property." Where used in this Privacy Policy, "MLB Entities" means MLB, the Office of the Commissioner of Baseball, the MLB Clubs, MLB Professional Development Leagues, LLC (“MLB PDL”), the MiLB Clubs, Major League Baseball Properties, Inc., The MLB Network, LLC, and Tickets.com, LLC. This Privacy Policy describes what information we collect via the MLB Properties, how we may use that information, when and to whom it may be disclosed, and the choices we offer for you to manage the personal information we collect related to your use of the MLB Properties. This Privacy Policy does not apply to the collection of information from you by MLB Clubs and/or MiLB Clubs offline (e.g., when you provide information over the phone or on a paper form). Certain MLB Club and/or MiLB Club offline privacy practices may be available for review within ballparks or at the ballpark information page located on the respective MLB Club and MiLB Club websites. This Privacy Policy does not apply to information about the MLB Entities’ employees, contractors, agents, and job applicants in their capacity as such. The MLB Properties may link to services or properties operated by Other Companies (e.g., the official photo store of Major League Baseball) which are not subject to this Privacy Policy. You should familiarize yourself with the privacy practices of any Other Company whose services or properties you utilize and direct any concerns regarding any such Other Company property to the administrator of the applicable property.

1. **[Personal Information We Collect](#section-1)**
2. **[How, and for What Purpose, We Use and Disclose Your Personal Information](#section-2)**
3. **[Other Information Collected](#section-3)**
4. **[Other Circumstances When Your Data May Be Disclosed](#section-4)**
5. **[Transferring Your Personal Information Across Borders](#section-5)**
6. **[Managing Your Personal Information](#section-6)**
7. **[California, Virginia, Colorado, Connecticut, Utah, and Texas Privacy Rights; Notice to Illinois Residents](#section-7)**
8. **[Other Information; Contact Us](#section-8)**

* * *

1\. Personal Information We Collect
-----------------------------------

We Collect Personal Information You Choose To Provide. You may visit and enjoy many elements of the MLB Properties without disclosing any personal information about yourself. However, if you choose to make use of select, special or enhanced elements of the MLB Properties, you may need to disclose with us certain personal information so those elements may function properly. When you use certain enhanced elements within the MLB Properties (e.g., create a profile, register for a promotion, make a purchase or publish a comment), the personal information we collect may include, but is not limited to:

* Full name,
* Email address,
* Password,
* Street address,
* Telephone number(s),
* Birth date,
* Payment data,
* IP addresses,
* Location data,
* Contacts (as stored in your wireless device),
* Demographic data,
* Device data,
* Usage data,
* Voice recordings,
* Audiovisual recordings,
* Information about your interests and preferences,
* Data specifically requested in relation to an activity or an event (e.g., emergency contact information),
* Data provided by Other Companies if you choose to connect your use of our services through the Other Company’s service,
* Personal information of a child if and only if a parent or guardian provides the child’s personal information; and
* Sensitive personal information.

If we collect your information, in most instances, the applicable page(s) or location(s) within the MLB Property will include statements regarding what information is required and functionality for you to submit required or requested information.

2\. How, and for What Purpose, We Use and Disclose Your Personal Information
----------------------------------------------------------------------------

If you submit personal information to us, or to any Other Company acting on our behalf (a "Service Provider"), via the MLB Properties, we may use and disclose your information as set forth in this Privacy Policy, as disclosed when you first submit your information or as otherwise permissible under applicable law. We will not sell, lease, publish, disclose or share your personal information with or to anyone else, except as set forth in this Privacy Policy. We may use and disclose your personal information as described in Section 1 above and:

* To provide you with information you have requested, or with products, services or content you have purchased, used or otherwise engaged with (e.g., a sweepstakes, rewards program, subscription to goods or services, etc.) and to communicate with you (including via postal mail) about the same;
* To communicate with you about the league or MLB Club(s)/MiLB Club(s) applicable to your interactions with the MLB Properties and about products, services, sponsors, partners or affiliates related to a purchase you have made or rules or terms to which you have agreed, to the extent the sending of such communication is permissible under applicable law;
* With one or more MLB Clubs/MiLB Clubs or other MLB Entities, to the extent you've submitted information or accessed functionality or content that relates specifically to such MLB/MiLB Club(s) or other MLB Entities (e.g., you've asked to receive the email newsletter of an MLB Club or you've made an MiLB Club-specific purchase), so we and they may learn more about fans like you, add your current or updated mailing address to the MLB/MiLB Club's postal mail list, and provide better services to you;
* To send you periodic surveys to help improve the MLB Properties or your Major League/Minor League Baseball experience;
* In connection with loyalty, membership or rewards programs operated or accessible from the MLB Properties;
* When the personally identifying components of your information are removed, we may use and disclose such anonymized information for internal purposes amongst MLB Entities (e.g., to learn about the age distribution of our users);
* In accordance with any other permission you provide at the time you submit such information to us; and
* To provide your personal information to other MLB Entities where necessary for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy.

For customers in the EEA, we are required to give you information about the legal basis on which we process your personal information. In some cases, such as where you have purchased a service, the processing of your personal information will be necessary in order to perform a contract with you. In many other cases, the processing will be necessary for the purpose of legitimate interests we are pursuing, namely the facilitation of the purposes for which your personal information is processed as set out above.

3\. Other Information Collected
-------------------------------

**Technical Information.** When you use the MLB Properties, we use software tools, including but not limited to cookies (small amounts of data which include a unique string of characters sent to your browser or application from a website’s computers and stored on your computer’s or device’s hard drive), web beacons (technology used to track activity, also known as pixel tags) and similar technologies, to collect a variety of information, for example the IP address of the computer or device used to access an MLB Property, the type of Internet browser or operating system used to access an MLB Property, the date and duration of a Website visit or the IP address used to access the Website. We use such technical information for internal purposes, for example to study and improve the response times of our Website. We may associate such technical information with personal information you provide to us as described in Section 1 above, in which case we will treat such associated information as personal information. Please be advised that associating technical information with personal information may be required for us, and our Service Providers, to recognize you and your communications with us, for example to retain your newsletter preferences or enable your use of a “shopping cart.” Customers within the EEA will be asked for consent prior to the setting of cookies.

**Location Data.** When you use an MLB Property via a wireless device we may solicit your permission to collect your location data. Some features within our Applications (e.g., live Major League/Minor League Baseball game video or location-based offers) may only function upon confirmation of your location, and therefore such features will not be available if you choose not to provide your location data to us. The specificity of the location data collected may depend on a number of factors, including the device you are using (e.g., laptop, smartphone, tablet) and how you are connected to the Internet (e.g., via cable broadband connection, Wi-Fi). If you enable location services for our Applications, we may collect location data (e.g., zip code) periodically as you use or leave open our Applications. We use such location information for internal purposes and to improve your MLB Property experience, for example to understand where our users are most successfully accessing the MLB Properties. We may associate such location information with personal information you provide to us as described in Section 1 above, in which case we will treat such associated information as personal information. Depending on the platform you use to access our Applications (e.g., Apple’s iOS, Google’s Android) you may be able to control whether location data is collected from within “Settings” or other controls on your wireless device or the Applications.

**Our Access to Your Contacts.** When you use our Games, we may solicit your permission to access your contacts list (e.g., address book) so you can be matched with individuals from your contacts list who participate in our Games and you can invite your friends to play. We will not store the information in your contacts list except to manage your Game invitations.

**Other Companies’ Cookies and Web Beacons; Network Advertisers; Targeted Advertising.** We allow and use select Service Providers and/or Other Companies that may act as third parties as defined under applicable data privacy laws, such as those who deliver advertisements, content, or social networking or which provide other services associated with the MLB Properties, to collect data and/or serve ads when you visit MLB Properties. We may also make available certain data you have given to us (e.g., IP address) or that we have collected through publicly available means to third parties engaged in targeting advertisements on the MLB Properties including for use in accordance with such third party's privacy policy. Network advertisers may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to MLB Properties in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. This may happen through permission given to such third parties to set cookies, web beacons or similar technologies in certain locations within the MLB Properties, including but not limited to certain of our emails. Third party companies that manage and deliver advertisements to websites and applications such as ours are commonly referred to as "network advertisers." A permitted network advertiser may use cookies, web beacons or similar technologies to collect information about your interaction with the MLB Properties in order to tailor certain advertisements and content delivered within the MLB Properties and on other websites within such network advertiser's ad network. These companies may also use non-cookie technologies to recognize your computer or device and/or to collect and record information about your web surfing activity including your activities on or off MLB Properties. Please keep in mind that your web browser may not permit you to block the use of these non-cookie technologies, and those browser settings that block cookies may have no effect on such techniques. You may learn more about network advertising industry practices and opt out of targeted behavioral advertising from many major third party network advertisers and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies via the information and tools available [here](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/) and [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/)at _http://www.aboutads.info/choices/_ and _http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/_.

To facilitate the activity described above and below, we use a Service Providers to convert your email address into a unique code (hashed email address or telephone number), which is then provided to the advertiser, Other Companies, including Other Companies that may act as third parties as defined under applicable data privacy laws, and/or Service Providers as set forth in this Privacy Policy.

**Other Advertising.** We disclose certain data to Social Networks (as defined below) such as Twitter, Facebook, LinkedIn and Snapchat to allow us to target existing users and customers with highly relevant advertising campaigns. We will not share your name, address, email address or telephone number for the purposes of such campaigns. Instead, a unique code (hashed email address) is disclosed to the applicable Social Network in order for that identifier to be matched against existing users of the relevant Social Network and to identify potentially relevant audiences for targeted advertising. We use services such as LinkedIn Matched Audiences and Facebook Custom Audiences for these purposes. If you do not wish to receive advertisements in this way, please follow the links in the paragraph above.

In addition to advertisements for our own goods and services, we may also facilitate Other Companies, including Other Companies that may act as third parties as defined under applicable data privacy laws, to advertise their own and/or Other Companies’ goods and services including by targeting those advertisements to those that might be most interested in them. These advertisements may be shown within our Games. This is done using information which does not include your name, address, email address or telephone number and we will not share or sell any of your personal information to third party advertisers other than as set forth in this Privacy Policy. In order to provide advertisements relevant to you, your IP address will be used, as well as your operating system and device type. Information about your particular device will be used to show you advertisements which work properly on that device.

**Social Networking.** When using the MLB Properties or when using certain Other Companies’ social networking services (e.g., Facebook, Twitter, Google +) (each a “Social Network”), you may have the option to connect your MLB Property information and activity with your Social Network information and activity. If you authorize such a connection, you permit us to disclose, share and/or publish information about your MLB Property activity with that Social Network and its users, and to access certain of your Social Network information, as disclosed to you at the time you consent to the connection. Information we may share with a Social Network may include, but is not limited to, technical information about your MLB Property activity, your MLB Property comments or the videos you watch on MLB Properties. Information we may access about you, with your consent, from a Social Network may include, but is not limited to, your basic Social Network information, your location data, your list of contacts, friends or followers and certain information about your activities on the Social Network. If you permit a connection between a Social Network and an MLB Property, we (and that Social Network) may be able to identify you and to associate information received pursuant to the connection with information we already have about you. We recommend that you familiarize yourself with the Privacy Policy and privacy control options of any Social Network with which you choose to disclose information or connect to an MLB Property.

**Device ID.** When you use certain MLB Properties, we or our Service Provider may collect your unique Device ID. We may use such information for internal purposes and to provide you a better MLB Property experience, for example to troubleshoot Application problems you may experience or provide you rewards or offers in connection with your Game activity. We may associate Device ID with personal information you provide to us as described in Section 1 above, in which case we will treat such associated information as personal information. You may learn more about our Service Provider for Mobile Games and opt out of any anonymous Device ID collection via the privacy settings available within your mobile device.

**AR Data.** If you authorize Apple’s TrueDepth Camera in connection with your use of the MLB Properties, we will capture information regarding that use and we may use and disclose such information as set forth in this Privacy Policy, as disclosed when you first authorize use of Apple’s TrueDepth Camera or as otherwise permissible under applicable law. Information from Apple’s TrueDepth camera is used in real time—we do not store this information on our servers or disclose it to Other Companies.

**Video and Audiovisual Recordings.** While you are present at facilities, games or events operated or controlled by MLB, an MLB Club, an MiLB Club, or an MLB Entity, there may be video recording, including but not limited to for telecast, security, marketing, promotional or other purposes. The terms and conditions applicable to your access to the applicable facility, game or event may include terms regarding the capture and use of video or audiovisual recordings and you should familiarize yourself with those terms. Furthermore, at certain games or events operated by MLB, an MLB Club, an MiLB Club, or any MLB Entity, consent may be separately sought for the capture and use of video or audiovisual content for purposes set forth in that consent. This video or audiovisual content may be utilized by MLB, an MLB Club, an MiLB Club, or an MLB Entity pursuant to this Privacy Policy to produce, exhibit, advertise or otherwise use your image, voice or likeness in any and all media now or existing in future as part of the MLB Entities’ commercial, advertising and marketing activities. It may also be used to provide security services, to train personnel regarding security practices and in connection with legal action or regulatory investigation. You may also elect to provide us with Submitted Content (as defined in the [Terms of Use](https://www.mlb.com/official-information/terms-of-use)), and consent to their use for marketing, promotional or other purposes, and otherwise pursuant to this Privacy Policy, on certain applicable MLB Properties and/or via applicable Social Networks.

**Biometric Information.** If you elect to participate in certain programs offered by the MLB Entities (e.g., Go Ahead Entry), the MLB Entities and/or their Service Provider(s) may perform a scan or collect imagery of your physical characteristics to create a unique identifier associated with you based on biometric identifiers. The terms and conditions applicable to such programs (e.g., Go Ahead Entry) may include terms regarding the capture and use of this biometric information, and you should familiarize yourself with those terms if you elect to utilize and engage with any such programs.

4\. Other Circumstances When Your Data May Be Disclosed
-------------------------------------------------------

* As with many websites, we use Google Analytics to understand how you and other visitors engage with MLB Properties, and we may enable Google Analytics advertising features to tailor certain advertisements and content delivered within the MLB Properties and/or third-party websites to you in accordance with the relevant sections of this Privacy Policy. If you don't want Analytics to be used in your browser, you can install the Google Analytics browser add-on ([here](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout)_https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout_). You can learn more about Google Analytics and privacy [here](https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245?hl=en)at _https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245?hl=en_.
* When you use the MLB Properties, we may disclose information that we may collect from you, such as your email (in hashed form), IP address or information about your browser or operating system, with our partner/service provider, LiveRamp Inc and its group companies (“LiveRamp”). LiveRamp may use MLB’s first party cookie on your browser to match your disclosed information to LiveRamp’s information in order to provide MLB with a pseudonymous identifier MLB uses in certain real time bidding digital advertising transactions. These Other Companies may in turn link further demographic or interest-based information to your browser. You can learn more and opt out of this use here: [https://liveramp.com/opt\_out/](https://liveramp.com/opt_out/)_https://liveramp.com/opt\_out/_.
* Aggregated and Anonymous Information. We may disclose aggregated, anonymous information to any Other Company. This information is not linked to personal information that can identify you or another individual person. Amongst other reasons, this information may be disclosed for advertising analytics purposes.
* Business Transfers. As time passes, MLB may disclose personal information with any person or party to whom we may transfer any of our rights or obligations under any agreement, or in connection with a sale, merger or consolidation of our business or other transfer of our assets, whether voluntarily or by operation of law, or to any person who is otherwise deemed to be our successor or transferee.
* Disclosure for Legal Purposes. We may be required to disclose your personal and non-personal information pursuant to judicial or governmental subpoenas, warrants or orders. If we are required to do so, we will, of course, obey the law. In addition, notwithstanding any term to the contrary in this Privacy Policy, we reserve the right to use, disclose or share your personal and non-personal information in order to investigate, prevent or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the safety of any person, violations of [MLB Terms of Use](https://www.mlb.com/official-information/terms-of-use) or as required by law.

5\. Transferring Your Personal Information Across Borders
---------------------------------------------------------

For customers in the EEA we are obliged to provide certain information relating to the transfer of your personal information outside the EEA. Where you have purchased a service, it may often be necessary to transfer your personal information in order to perform a contract with you. In addition, we may in some circumstances rely on your express consent. If you submit personal information to us, or to a Service Provider, via the MLB Properties, you will be voluntarily transferring this personal information to the United States, a jurisdiction which does not provide the same framework as the EEA for the protection of personal information. The same will be the case in relation to your personal information which is collected when you use MLB Properties as specified above.

6\. Managing Your Personal Information
--------------------------------------

You may choose and control what information you provide about yourself and certain information which is automatically collected via the MLB Properties. If you do not wish to provide certain information necessary for enhanced functionality or content on the MLB Properties, please do not use such functionality or content. Remember that when you disclose information publicly online, it may be indexable by search engines or recorded by others, and any search engine index or record of your information may persist after you delete the information at the original source.

#### Accounts Through MLB Website

If you have registered for an account through our Website, you may review and revise certain of your account information by [clicking here](https://www.mlb.com/login)visiting _https://www.mlb.com/login_ to log in, and then navigating the left-hand menu options. You may modify your subscriptions to our various promotional email communications and newsletters by accessing the "Email Subscriptions" section within your Website account.

#### Cookies

If you do not want information collected through the use of cookies, there is a simple procedure in most browsers that allows a user to accept or reject most cookies. Certain cookies that are set when you access certain video products via the MLB Properties, called local shared objects or Flash cookies, may not be managed using the settings in your web browser. Information on managing, accepting and rejecting these cookies is available from Adobe on the [Adobe Website](https://www.adobe.com/privacy/opt-out.html)Adobe Website available at _https://www.adobe.com/privacy/opt-out.html_. If you set your browser or Adobe Flash options not to accept cookies or local shared objects, you may not be able to take advantage of certain features of the MLB Properties.

#### Personal Information Provided During Website Registration

If you want to review or revise the personal information you provided during Website registration or in connection with certain Website purchases, or change the promotional email communications or newsletters you receive from us, you may [click here](https://www.mlb.com/login)visit _https://www.mlb.com/login_ to log in, and then click on the applicable left-hand menu option(s). If you want to review or revise other personal information you have provided to us, or to close your account(s) and have us delete the applicable account personal information (except what is needed for record-keeping purposes) call Customer Service at 866-244-2291 (within the United States) or 1-315-203-6761 (outside the United States).

#### Customers in the EEA

For customers in the EEA, you have the right to see a copy of the personal information that we hold about you, and you may ask us to make any necessary changes to ensure that this information is accurate and kept up to date. To exercise these privacy rights, please [click here](https://privacyportal.onetrust.com/webform/53a301ae-6882-46f9-af93-24f64f792aee/e335fc4a-1f05-405e-af22-0782e613c64b)visit _https://privacyportal.onetrust.com/webform/53a301ae-6882-46f9-af93-24f64f792aee/e335fc4a-1f05-405e-af22-0782e613c64b_.

In addition, subject to limitations as provided for by applicable data protection legislation you have the right to request the erasure of your personal information or the restriction of its processing, or the transfer of your personal information to another data controller. Please contact us as specified below if you wish to do so.

#### How Long MLB Retains Your Personal Information

We retain your personal information for as long as reasonably necessary and proportionate to achieve the purposes and uses set out in this Privacy Policy, as authorized by law, and to meet legal, taxation, accounting, risk management or business requirements. Different retention periods apply to different types of records and data and, where information is used for more than one purpose, we will retain it until the purpose with the latest period expires. The criteria used to determine our retention periods include: (i) the length of time we have an ongoing relationship with you and provide products, services or content to you; (ii) whether there is a legal obligation that applies to us; and (iii) whether we determine we need to retain the information due to our legal position, including, but not limited to relevant statutes of limitations, litigation, or regulatory investigations.

These retention periods may be extended where circumstances so require or until a particular query, investigation or dispute is fully resolved.

7\. Your California, Virginia, Colorado, Connecticut, Utah, and Texas Privacy Rights; Notice to Illinois Residents
------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

If you are a resident of California, you have certain rights pursuant to the California Consumer Privacy Act (“CCPA”), as amended by the California Privacy Rights Act of 2020 (“CPRA”), and the Shine the Light law. Except where specifically noted below, both the CCPA and the CPRA are collectively referred to as the CCPA in this Privacy Policy. Those rights are detailed in this Section 7. To exercise the rights detailed in this Section 7, please [click here](https://privacyportal.onetrust.com/webform/53a301ae-6882-46f9-af93-24f64f792aee/0b9faea2-b2d3-4f5d-84d2-1c523a648a05) or call us at 866-800-1275.

If you are a resident of Virginia, you have certain rights pursuant to the Virginia Consumer Data Protection Act. Those rights are detailed in this Section 7. To exercise the rights detailed in this Section 7, please [click here](https://privacyportal.onetrust.com/webform/53a301ae-6882-46f9-af93-24f64f792aee/55ff8eb2-e3ad-42b9-b009-7ad5d05eeae8) or call us at 866-800-1275.

If you are a resident of Colorado, you have certain rights pursuant to the Colorado Privacy Act. Those rights are detailed in this Section 7. To exercise the rights detailed in this Section 7, please [click here](https://privacyportal.onetrust.com/webform/53a301ae-6882-46f9-af93-24f64f792aee/ecfeb5d8-d958-4836-a2f6-4c5b5c7d1799) or call us at 866-800-1275.

If you are a resident of Connecticut, you have certain rights pursuant to the Connecticut Data Privacy Act. Those rights are detailed in this Section 7. To exercise the rights detailed in this Section 7, please [click here](https://privacyportal.onetrust.com/webform/53a301ae-6882-46f9-af93-24f64f792aee/f3aa1439-1739-4692-8870-143108ae9d3e) or call us at 866-800-1275.

If you are a resident of Utah, you have certain rights pursuant to the Utah Consumer Privacy Act. Those rights are detailed in this Section 7. To exercise the rights detailed in this Section 7, please [click here](https://privacyportal.onetrust.com/webform/53a301ae-6882-46f9-af93-24f64f792aee/69704df2-ec74-4501-807c-e6965552c84c) or call us at 866-800-1275.

If you are a resident of Texas, you have certain rights pursuant to the Texas Data Privacy and Security Act. Those rights are detailed in this Section 7. To exercise the rights detailed in this Section 7, please [click here](https://privacyportal.onetrust.com/webform/53a301ae-6882-46f9-af93-24f64f792aee/96e0b29a-b491-4075-964c-918e25c142c6) or call us at 866-800-1275.

Your privacy rights include (i) the right to know about your personal information that MLB collected, disclosed, sold or shared; (ii) the right to delete your personal information; (iii) the right to correct inaccuracies in your personal information; (iv) the right to opt-out of sale or sharing of your personal information; (v) the right to opt-out of targeted advertising; (vi) the right to data portability; (vii) the right to non-discrimination; and (viii) the right to appeal a refusal to act on your data rights request.

### A. Right to Know About Personal Information Collected, Disclosed, Sold or Shared

You have the right to request that MLB disclose the following information to you about our collection and use of your personal information in connection with the MLB Properties over the last 12 months:

* The categories of personal information we collect about you.
* The categories of sources for the personal information we collect about you.
* Our business or commercial purpose for collecting or selling that personal information.
* The categories of third parties with whom we share that personal information for cross-context behavioral advertising.
* The specific pieces of personal information collected about you.
* If we sold or disclosed your personal information for a business purpose, (i) a list of the categories of personal information we have sold in the prior 12 months and (ii) a list of the categories of personal information we have disclosed in the prior 12 months.
* If we have not sold or disclosed your personal information in the preceding 12 months, we will disclose that upon request.

You also have the right to request that MLB disclose the following information to you about our collection and use of your sensitive personal information in connection with the MLB Properties over the last 12 months:

* The categories of sensitive personal information we collect about you.
* The categories of sources for the sensitive personal information we collect about you.

For California residents, our responses to right to know requests will cover the personal information we have collected and maintain about the consumer on or after January 1, 2022, or for a shorter period if an exemption applies or if requested by the consumer.

### B. Right to Request Deletion of Personal Information

You also have the right to request that MLB delete any of your personal information that we collected via the MLB Properties and retained. We will not delete your information if we need it to protect the security, integrity or functionality of our operations and systems, to comply with legal obligations, to provide you with a good or service you requested, or for certain other reasons.

### C. Right to Request Correction of Personal Information

You have the right to request that MLB correct inaccuracies in your personal information that we collect and maintain about you. If MLB receives a verifiable consumer request to correct inaccurate personal information, we will use commercially reasonable efforts to correct the inaccurate personal information as directed by you. We will not be able to update your information if we need it to protect the security or functionality of our operations, to comply with legal obligations, or for certain other reasons.

### D. Process MLB will use to Verify Request to Disclose, Correct, or Delete Personal Information of a California, Virginia, Colorado, Connecticut or Utah Resident

A request to disclose, correct or delete your personal information must provide sufficient information that allows us to reasonably verify you are the person about whom we collected personal information and that you are a resident of California, Virginia, Colorado, Connecticut or Utah, as applicable. Your request must describe your request with sufficient detail that allows us to properly understand, evaluate, and respond to it. We will only use personal information provided in a verifiable consumer request to verify the requestor’s identity or authority to make the request. We ordinarily process requests within 45 days of its receipt. In some cases, we may extend this period to 90 calendar days. If we require more than 45 days, we will inform you or your authorized agent in writing of the reason we did so and the extension period.

### E. Right to Opt-Out of the Sale or Sharing of Personal Information

You have the right to direct us at any time to not sell your personal information or share your personal information for cross-context behavioral advertising. You may submit an opt-out request by [clicking here](https://www.mlb.com/do-not-sell-or-share-my-personal-data), by clicking on the “Do Not Sell or Share My Personal Information” link on our homepage, or by dialing 866-800-1275.

### F. Right to Opt-Out of Targeted Advertising

You have the right to direct us not to process your personal information for targeted advertising. You may submit an opt-out request by [clicking here](https://www.mlb.com/do-not-sell-or-share-my-personal-data), by clicking on the “Do Not Sell or Share My Personal Information” link on our homepage, or by dialing 866-800-1275.

### G. Your Right to Data Portability

You have the right to have a copy of personal information that MLB collected and maintains about you transferred to you or to another authorized party.

### H. Your Right to Non-Discrimination for the Exercise of Your Privacy Rights

We will not deny services, charge different prices, offer a different quality of service or otherwise discriminate against you for exercising your California, Virginia, Colorado, Connecticut or Utah privacy rights, as applicable. Nothing in this section prohibits MLB from charging you a different price or rate, or from providing a different level or quality of goods or services to you, if that difference is reasonably related to the value provided to you by the use of your data. With your consent, MLB may choose to offer you financial incentives directly related to the value of your personal information for the collection, sale, or deletion of your personal information.

### I. Information Regarding Authorized Agents

You may designate an authorized agent to make a request on your behalf. If you choose to do so, MLB may require you to (1) provide the authorized agent written permission to do so and (2) verify your own identity and residency directly. MLB may deny a request from an agent that does not submit proof that they have been authorized by the consumer to act on their behalf.

### J. Right to Appeal

If you are a Colorado, Virginia or Connecticut resident, and MLB denies your request to exercise any of the data rights described above, you have the right to appeal our decision within a reasonable period of time after your receipt of our decision.

You may appeal our decision by sending an email to [dataprivacy@mlb.com](mailto:dataprivacy@mlb.com). We will respond to an appeal within 60 days of receipt for residents of Virginia, Texas and Connecticut, and within 45 days of receipt for residents of Colorado. We may extend the response period by 60 additional days for residents of Colorado where reasonably necessary and, if we extend the response period, we will inform you of the extension within 45 days after our receipt of your appeal. Our response to your appeal will inform you of decisions and actions in response to your appeal, including an explanation of the reasons for the decisions.

If you have concerns about the results of your appeal, you have the right to contact your state attorney general. If your appeal is denied and you are a Virginia resident, you may contact the Virginia Attorney General to submit a complaint at: [https://www.oag.state.va.us/consumer-protection/index.php/file-a-complaint](https://www.oag.state.va.us/consumer-protection/index.php/file-a-complaint)_https://www.oag.state.va.us/consumer-protection/index.php/file-a-complaint_. If your appeal is denied and you are a Connecticut resident, you may contact the Connecticut Attorney General to submit a complaint at: [https://portal.ct.gov/AG/Common/Complaint-Form-Landing-page](https://portal.ct.gov/AG/Common/Complaint-Form-Landing-page)_https://portal.ct.gov/AG/Common/Complaint-Form-Landing-page_. If your appeal is denied and you are a Texas resident, you may contact the Texas Attorney General to submit a complaint at [https://consumerprotection.texasattorneygeneral.gov/consumercomplaintportal/s/flow/TCP\_Complaint\_Input\_Data\_Privacy](https://consumerprotection.texasattorneygeneral.gov/consumercomplaintportal/s/flow/TCP_Complaint_Input_Data_Privacy)_https://consumerprotection.texasattorneygeneral.gov/consumercomplaintportal/s/flow/TCP\_Complaint\_Input\_Data\_Privacy_.

### K. Personal Information We Collect, Disclose, Sell, or Share of Personal Information

MLB has disclosed, sold or shared personal information to parties for a business or commercial purpose in the past 12 months. MLB does not knowingly sell or share the personal information of minors under 16 years of age without affirmative authorization.

These are the general categories of consumer personal information that MLB Entities have collected in the last 12 months, the sources from which that information was collected, the business purpose for which the information was collected, and the categories of parties with whom MLB Entities disclose, sell, or share personal information.

| Category of Personal Information Collected | Source(s) from which that Personal Information may be collected | Business Purpose | Categories of Service Providers and/or Other Companies to whom MLB Entities disclose this Personal Information | Categories of Third Parties to whom MLB Entities sell or share this Personal Information |
| --- | --- | --- | --- | --- |
| Full name | * MLB Properties (including but not limited to websites, apps, games, customer service)<br>* Ticketing partners (e.g., Tickets.com, Ticketmaster)<br>* E-commerce partners (e.g., MLBShop.com, Auctions, Snow Commerce, Fanatics)<br>* Social Media<br>* Partners and licensees | * Order fulfillment<br>* Subscription management<br>* Personalization<br>* Promotions | Partners and licensees  <br>  <br>Data processing and analytics vendors  <br>  <br>Fulfillment vendors  <br>  <br>Payment processors  <br>  <br>Service Providers such as website hosting, security and/or customer service vendors | None |
| Email address | * MLB Properties<br>* Ticketing partners<br>* E-commerce partners<br>* Social Media<br>* Partners and licensees | * Order fulfillment<br>* Subscription management<br>* Security and access control<br>* Provision of services purchased or requested | Partners and licensees  <br>  <br>Data processing and analytics vendors  <br>  <br>Fulfillment vendors  <br>  <br>Payment processors  <br>  <br>Service Providers such as website hosting, security and/or customer service vendors | None |
| Password | * MLB Properties<br>* Ticketing partners | * Security and access control<br>* Provision of services purchased or requested | Service Providers providing security and access control services | None |
| Street Address | * MLB Properties<br>* Ticketing partners<br>* E-commerce partners<br>* Social Media<br>* Partners and licensees | * Order fulfillment<br>* Subscription management | Partners and licensees  <br>  <br>Data processing and analytics vendors  <br>  <br>Fulfillment vendors  <br>  <br>Payment processors  <br>  <br>Service Providers such as website hosting, security and/or customer service vendors | None |
| Telephone number | * MLB Properties<br>* Ticketing partners<br>* E-commerce partners<br>* Partners and licensees | * Order fulfillment<br>* Subscription management<br>* Provide requested information<br>* Promotion | Data processing and analytics vendors  <br>  <br>Fulfillment vendors  <br>  <br>Service Providers such as website hosting, security and/or customer service vendors | None |
| Birth date / age | * MLB Properties<br>* Ticketing partners<br>* E-commerce partner<br>* Social Media<br>* Partners and licensees | * Security and access control<br>* Provision of services purchased or requested<br>* Legal compliance | Partners and licensees  <br>  <br>Data processing and analytics vendors  <br>  <br>Fulfillment vendors  <br>  <br>Service Providers such as website hosting, security and/or customer service vendors | None |
| Payment data | * MLB Properties<br>* Ticketing partners<br>* E-commerce partner | * Order fulfillment<br>* Subscription management | Payment processors | None |
| Hashed emails and/or phone numbers | * MLB Properties<br>* Ticketing partners<br>* E-commerce partners<br>* Social Media<br>* Partners and licensees | * Provide requested services<br>* Deliver advertising | Data processing and analytics vendors  <br>  <br>Advertising vendors | Advertising vendors |
| Hashed biometric information | * Biometric authentication services vendor | * Provide requested services | Service Providers such as website hosting, security and/or customer service vendors | None |
| IP address / Device ID | * MLB Properties<br>* Ticketing partners<br>* E-commerce partner<br>* Social Media<br>* Advertising vendors (e.g., Google) | * Provide requested services<br>* Deliver advertising | Data processing and analytics vendors  <br>  <br>Advertising vendors  <br>  <br>Service Providers such as website hosting, security and/or customer service vendors | Advertising vendors  <br>  <br>Advertisers |
| Location data | * MLB Properties<br>* Ticketing partners<br>* E-commerce partners<br>* Social Media<br>* Advertising vendors | * Providing services (e.g., MLB.TV, MiLB.TV) that are location dependent<br>* Delivering personalized experiences<br>* Providing improved experiences and products<br>* Promotions and advertising | Data processing and analytics vendors  <br>  <br>Advertising vendors  <br>  <br>Service Providers such as website hosting, security and/or customer service vendors | Advertising vendors  <br>  <br>Advertisers |
| Demographic data | * MLB Properties<br>* Ticketing partners<br>* Social Media<br>* Third party data and analytics vendors | * Providing tailored services, experiences and products<br>* Improving services, experiences and products | Data processing and analytics vendors  <br>  <br>Advertising vendors  <br>  <br>Service Providers such as website hosting, security and/or customer service vendors | Advertising vendors  <br>  <br>Advertisers |
| Contact list | * MLB Properties (e.g., apps)<br>* Ticketing partners | * Providing requested services | Service Providers such as website hosting, security and/or customer service vendors |     |
| Cookie data | * MLB Properties<br>* Ticketing partners<br>* E-commerce partner<br>* Social Media | * Delivering optimized services, experiences and products<br>* Advertising | Advertising vendors  <br>  <br>Service Providers such as website hosting, security and/or customer service vendors | Advertising vendors  <br>  <br>Advertisers |
| Usage data | * MLB Properties<br>* Ticketing partners<br>* E-commerce partner<br>* Social Media | * Delivering optimized services, experiences and products<br>* Advertising | Data processing and analytics vendors  <br>  <br>Advertising vendors  <br>  <br>Service Providers such as website hosting, security and/or customer service vendors | Advertising vendors  <br>  <br>Advertisers |
| Data specific to an event, activity, or product (e.g., fan clubs, fantasy camps, 5k runs) | * MLB Properties<br>* Ticketing partners | * Order fulfillment<br>* Event operations<br>* Providing requested services | The entities producing the event or activity, if other than an MLB Entity  <br>  <br>Service Providers such as website hosting, security and/or customer service vendors | None |
| Preferences | * MLB Properties<br>* Ticketing partners<br>* Partners and licensees | * Providing services, products or subscriptions<br>* Tailoring products and services in accordance with preferences | Data processing and analytics vendors  <br>  <br>Service Providers such as website hosting, security and/or customer service vendors | Advertising vendors  <br>  <br>Advertisers |
| Audio and/or audio-visual recordings | * MLB Properties<br>* Social Media<br>* Partners and licensees | * Providing requested services<br>* To produce, exhibit, advertise or otherwise use your image, voice or likeness in any and all media now or existing in future as part of the MLB Entities’ commercial, advertising and marketing activities; and<br>* in the case of images or footage captured on CCTV cameras to ensure the safety of the venues hosting MLB/MiLB games and/or events and of individuals attending MLB/MiLB games and/or events. | Partners and licensees  <br>  <br>Service Providers such as website hosting, security and/or customer service vendors | None |

These are the categories of sensitive consumer personal information that MLB Entities has collected in the last 12 months, the sources from which that information was collected, the business purpose for which the information was collected, and the categories of third parties with whom MLB Entities disclose, sell, or share sensitive personal information.

MLB does not use sensitive personal information to infer characteristics about you for purposes other than those permitted by applicable law, including the CCPA and its regulations. MLB typically limits its use and disclosure of sensitive personal information to the following purposes: (1) to perform services, such as to provide benefits to consumers; (2) to resist deceptive, fraudulent, or illegal actions; (3) to ensure the physical safety of our personnel, customers, visitors, and others; and (4) to provide short-term, transient and non-personalized advertising.

| Category of Sensitive Personal Information Collected | Source(s) from which that Sensitive Personal Information may be collected | Business Purpose | Categories of Other Companies to whom MLB Entities disclose, this Sensitive Personal Information | Categories of Third Parties to whom MLB Entities sell or share this Sensitive Personal Information |
| --- | --- | --- | --- | --- |
| MLB.com account credentials | * MLB Properties<br>* Ticketing partners<br>* E-commerce partners<br>* Partners and licensees | * Providing requested services<br>* Order fulfillment<br>* Subscription management<br>* Security and access control<br>* Provision of services purchased or requested | Service Providers providing security and access control services | None |
| Racial or ethnic origin | * MLB Properties<br>* Ticketing partners<br>* E-commerce partners | * Providing requested services<br>* Ensuring the diversity of community programs | Camp, clinic, and event production vendors  <br>  <br>Charitable partners (e.g., grantees of MLB/MiLB or MLB/MiLB Club foundations)  <br>  <br>Service Providers such as website hosting, security and/or customer service vendors | None |
| Precise geolocation information | * MLB Properties<br>* Ticketing partners<br>* E-commerce partners<br>* Social Media<br>* Advertising vendors | * Providing services (e.g., MLB.TV) that are location dependent<br>* Delivering personalized experiences<br>* Providing improved experiences and products | Data processing and analytics vendors  <br>  <br>Service Providers providing location verification and related services | None |
| Health information | * MLB Properties<br>* Ticketing partners<br>* E-Commerce partners | * Providing requested services | Camp, clinic, and event production vendors  <br>  <br>Service Providers such as website hosting, security and/or customer service vendors | None |
| Biometric Information | * Biometric authentication services vendor | * Providing requested services | Service providers, such as the biometric authentication services vendor | None |

### L. California Privacy Rights Report of Metrics

Below reflects the number of requests from individuals related to the California Consumer Privacy Act received and processed by MLB and the MLB/MiLB Clubs during the period of time noted below. These numbers will be updated at least annually (with the date of such update, and prior update, noted below):

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| Requests to Know Personal Information | Received: 140  <br>Complied with (in whole or in part): 105  <br>Denied: 35 |
| Requests to Delete Personal Information | Received: 368  <br>Complied with (in whole or in part): 71  <br>Denied: 297 |
| Requests to Correct Personal Information | Received: 4  <br>Complied with (in whole or in part): 0  <br>Denied: 4 |
| Requests to Opt Out of Sale or Sharing of Personal Information | Received: 57,866  <br>Complied with (in whole or in part): 57,866  <br>Denied: 0 |
| Requests to Limit Use and Disclosure of Sensitive Personal Information | Received: N/A  <br>Complied with (in whole or in part): N/A  <br>Denied: N/A |
| The median number of days within which MLB substantively responded to requests to know, delete, and opt-out of sale is: 0.71 days |     |
| Most recent update: March 1, 2024  <br>Prior update: March 1, 2023 |     |

### M. Shine the Light Law

If you are a resident of California, pursuant to California Civil Code Section 1798.83, you may request information regarding our disclosure of your personal information to a third party for that party's direct marketing purposes. Any such disclosure made to a third party by us would be otherwise in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy. To make such a request please **[click here](https://privacyportal-cdn.onetrust.com/dsarwebform/53a301ae-6882-46f9-af93-24f64f792aee/0b9faea2-b2d3-4f5d-84d2-1c523a648a05.html)** or write to us at: MLB Advanced Media, L.P., Privacy Administrator, 1271 Avenue of the Americas, New York, New York 10020.

### N. Do Not Track Requests

“Do Not Track” signals are options on your browser that inform website operators that you would not like to have your online activity tracked. Currently, there is no industry standard regarding any appropriate action that websites should take when they receive “Do Not Track” signals. As there is no industry standard, please note that we do not alter our Website’s data and information collection and use practices when we receive a “Do Not Track” signal from your browser.

### O. Loyalty Program Disclosures

If you are a resident of California or Colorado and you participate in a loyalty, rewards, premium feature, discount, or club card program established by an MLB Entity for the purpose of providing discounts, rewards, or other value to you in connection with your participation (each, if any, a “Loyalty Program”), we may disclose and/or share your personal information as set forth in this Privacy Policy and/or pursuant to any separate consent you may provide in connection with your participation in the Loyalty Program. You may cease your participation in any Loyalty Program at any time by following the instructions provided in connection with the Loyalty Program or by contacting 866-800-1275.

### P. Notice to Illinois Residents

If you are a resident of Illinois and you elect to participate in any program or offering requiring you to provide biometric information to any MLB Entity or its Service Provider(s), MLB will permanently destroy such biometric information, and any information directly derived from such biometric information, when the initial purpose for collecting or obtaining such information has been satisfied or within three (3) years following your last interaction with us, whichever occurs first.

8\. Other Information; Contact Us
---------------------------------

* **No Spyware or Adware**. We do not install any Spyware or Adware in connection with the MLB Properties, or distribute any commercial message, or authorize any third party to distribute any commercial message, by means of Spyware or Adware. "Spyware" or "Adware" is any software which has been downloaded to or installed on an Internet user's computer or device, without the user's actual consent, and facilitates the distribution of any commercial message to the user. If you feel you may have Spyware from another company installed on your machine, there are various anti-Spyware/Adware software applications available on the Internet to identify if this has occurred.
* **Our Security Practices**. The account information associated with the MLB Properties is password protected for your privacy and security. You choose your password for the MLB Properties so the strength of that password is determined by you. We recommend that you choose a unique password and not share your password with anyone else. In certain areas, we use industry-standard SSL encryption to protect data transmissions.
* **Links**. The MLB Properties contain links to other websites and products produced by MLB and to websites and products operated by unrelated Other Companies. In addition, if you click on an advertisement within the MLB Properties, you may be directed to a web page within the MLB Properties or to a third party website or product. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of third party websites or products, and we encourage you to read the privacy policies of every website and product that collects personally identifiable information from you. This Privacy Policy applies only to the MLB Properties, unless you are notified otherwise upon accessing any third party website or product, in which case the terms and conditions set forth in such notification will apply.
* Your Nevada Privacy Rights. If you are a resident of Nevada, in accordance with Nevada Revised Statutes Chapter 603A, you may request that we do not sell certain of your personally identifiable information (your "Covered Information" as defined in NRS Chapter 603A) by sending a request to [dataprivacy@mlb.com](mailto:dataprivacy@mlb.com).
* **Special Rules For Children**. Because of federal law, we are not permitted to knowingly collect any personal information from a child under the age of thirteen without the consent of that child's parent or guardian. The statements in this Privacy Policy about our collection and use of personal information also apply to our treatment of personal information from children under the age of thirteen. Some elements of the MLB Properties (e.g., shop, ticketing, and auctions) require the submission of a payment card number along with personal information in connection with a purchase; other elements of the MLB Properties (e.g., fantasy baseball) require the submission of personal information to access or use the MLB Properties. Except in certain cases where limited contact information may be collected and not retained, these elements of the MLB Properties are not available to children under the age of thirteen. If a child who we know to be under the age of thirteen and for whom we have not received parental consent attempts to utilize a service on the MLB Properties which is not available to children, he/she will not be able to access it and may receive a message which relays that he/she is not eligible for such feature. For children located in jurisdictions within the EU or EEA, where this Privacy Policy refers to consent, this will require the consent of a parent or legal guardian in relation to any person under the age specified by the law applicable to the location of the child in question.
* **Contact Us Regarding Privacy**. If you have questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, you can contact us at:  
    MLB Advanced Media, L.P.  
    Privacy Administrator  
    1271 Avenue of the Americas  
    New York, NY 10020  
    _Phone_: (646) 495-4091  
    _Fax_: (212) 485-8111  
    _Email_: [dataprivacy@mlb.com](mailto:dataprivacy@mlb.com)
* **Notification of Changes**. If we make an important change to this Privacy Policy, we will post a notification and link within the MLB Properties so that you may review the updated Privacy Policy.

Major League Baseball
---------------------

* OFFICIAL INFORMATION
* HELP/CONTACT US
* MORE MLB SITES & AFFILIATES
* CAREERS
